streetfightmag.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Street Fight

_Hyperlocal Industries (“Street Fight”) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Street Fight website (the “Street Fight Site”), submitting information or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy._

**What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers Street Fight’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that Street Fight gathers when you are accessing the Street Fight Site and when you use the Street Fight services or register for events provided by Street Fight. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Street Fight’s treatment of any Personal Information that Street Fight’s business partners share with Street Fight. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Street Fight does not own or control, or to individuals that Street Fight does not employ or manage.

**What Personal Information Does Street Fight Collect?**

The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, website URL, e-mail address, blog or other personal website URL, your nickname or screenname, and any other information that would allow Street Fight to identify you or contact you if needed.

In addition to the Personal Information as listed above and below, we may ask you to provide certain other information such as general demographic information, including age, gender, ZIP code, preferences, and interests. The information we gather from our users enables us to personalize and improve our services.

We may receive and store any information you enter on the Street Fight Site or provide to us in any other way. The Personal Information you provide may be used for providing attribution to comments you post, to operate and improve the Street Fight Site, and to better deliver the our services.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our websites or services. Street Fight may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Street Fight cookie information, and the page you requested.

Street Fight uses “cookies” to collect non-personal data and information. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, and is typically placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The way cookies function is by assigning a number to the user that has no meaning outside of the assigning Web site.

You should be aware that Street Fight cannot control the use of cookies (or the resulting information) by Street Fight’s third-party partners or advertisers. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Street Fight sites and services that depend on cookies.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

Except as described in this Privacy Notice, your personal information will be used only by Street Fight and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates, and your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent. We share your Personal Information only with your consent or as described below:

Agents: We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Street Fight’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Street Fight, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Street Fight may continue to use your personal information.

**Personal Information as Set Forth in this Policy**

Protection of Street Fight and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Street Fight, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Security and Protection of Personal Information**

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and store Personal Information collected in a database. However, while we employ reasonable standards of security, no security system is impenetrable. For most internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions you transmit. As such, Street Fight cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to Street Fight over the internet. We recommend that you do not disclose your password or confirmation number (as applicable) to anyone.

**E-mail Communications**

Upon registration for events and/or services provided by Street Fight, we may send you daily or weekly e-mails. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at info@Street Fight.com and include sufficient information for us to identify your account, including your name, email address and the specifics of your request. However, after you unsubscribe to cease receiving e-mails, Street Fight may still contact you via e-mail for administrative or informational purposes, including messages regarding the administration of your account and/or any services or events to which you have registered.

**Advertisements Displayed by Third Parties**

Street Fight may allow third-party ad serving companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on the Street Fight Site. Ad serving companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you, and as such, they may be able to compile information over time about whether you reviewed or clicked on advertisements they display. These companies may use this information to display targeted advertisements and may associate this information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on participating advertisers’ websites. Street Fight has no access to or control over cookies of these links to other websites and organizations, nor does Street Fight have control over or access to cookies by Street Fight’s third-party partners or advertisers. This Privacy Policy does not cover any use of Personal Information that a third-party advertiser or ad server may collect from you.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Street Fight retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Street Fight Site, and such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. Your continued access or use of the website and/or the services shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any amendments and/or modifications.

**Questions or Comments Regarding this Privacy Policy**

Street Fight welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use of share your Personal Information. Any such questions or comments should be submitted via email to info@streetfightmag.com. We will make every effort to resolve or answer your concern.

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 11, 2012.
